Canciones
1Intro : Singularity 3’14”
2FAKE LOVE 4’06”
3The Truth Untold (Feat. Steve Aoki)4’02”
4134340 3’49”
5Paradise 3’30”
6Love Maze 3’40”
7Magic Shop 4’36”
8Airplane pt.2 3’39”
9Anpanman 3’54”
10So What 4’44”
11Outro : Tear 4’45”

ABOUT ALBUM
BTS releases third studio album LOVE YOURSELF 轉 ‘TEAR’
Fake love inevitably leads to loss and separation,
For true love can only begin when you learn to love yourself

BTS will release LOVE YOURSELF 轉 ‘TEAR’, their third studio album on May 18.

BTS’ LOVE YOURSELF series bears the message that loving oneself is the beginning of true love. Whereas the previously unveiled LOVE YOURSELF 起 ‘WONDER’ and LOVE YOURSELF 承 ‘HER’ albums expressed the heart-fluttering and tingling moments of love, LOVE YOURSELF 轉 ‘TEAR’ album embodies the pain of boys faced with parting.

About BTS
	BTS, an acronym of Bangtan Sonyeondan or “Beyond the Scene,” is a Grammy-nominated South Korean group that has been capturing the hearts of millions of fans globally since its debut in June 2013.
The members of BTS are RM, Jin, SUGA, j-hope, Jimin, V, and Jung Kook. Gaining recognition for their authentic and self-produced music, top-notch performances, and the way they interact with their fans, BTS has established themselves as “21st century Pop Icons” breaking countless world records. While imparting a positive influence through activities such as the LOVE MYSELF campaign and the UN ‘Speak Yourself’ speech, the band has mobilized millions of fans across the world (named ARMY), collected four No. 1 songs in a span of 9 months, performed multiple sold-out stadium shows across the world, and been named TIME’s Entertainer of the Year 2020. BTS has been nominated for Best Pop Duo/Group Performance for the 63rd Grammy Awards and recognized with numerous prestigious awards like the Billboard Music Awards, American Music Awards and MTV Video Music Awards.